Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
A Crisis Suddenly Emerges
Episode 1
Today’s meteor shower is so beautiful
Yes
Let’s come and make a wish
I hope to be
Weslie
Wolffy
It’s too dangerous here. Leave now.
There’s a crisis in the starry sky
Then what are we waiting for? Let’s go together as Defenders.
look at my frisbee
Is the space war fun?
Sorry Mr. Slowy
Okay, let’s continue the class
Just mentioned
Our universe is full of infinite possibilities
in other corners of the universe
There may also be various wonderful worlds
Is it like the Season Towns, Qimao Kingdom, and the Miaogou Kingdom?
Those belong to our world
But outside our universe
There are other more wonderful worlds
There are all kinds of strange scenery and strange creatures there
Then can we go on adventures to those wonderful worlds?
But these are still controversial
With our current technology, it is temporarily impossible to reach
Class ends.
Goodbye Mr. Slowy
You can dream without falling asleep. How do you do that?
It’s a space war
We also want to paint together
Okay
mushroom mushroom
Son, we bought a lot of mushrooms today
Mommy must be very happy
Let’s go home quickly, Daddy
You are finally back
Mom, look, we bought a lot of mushrooms
That’s awesome Wilie
You go and put the mushrooms in the kitchen first.
Okay
I’ll help too
What you need to help with is packing these things
Wolnie, these are my treasures
Broken toothbrush, rotten clothes, smelly shoes
These are also treasures?
Of course they are
Look at this toothbrush
It has adapted perfectly to my tooth shape
This dress is comfortable and breathable
These sneakers are very memorable.
You won’t throw these away, right?
Then throw it here
I haven’t sorted it out yet.
You actually secretly hid so many useless inventions
All these inventions are amazing.
This is awesome
Fortunately there was no explosion
This is my latest boomerang bomb invention
It can be thrown out and fly back again, and the explosion is very powerful.
is very dangerous
It’s so dangerous. How do you want to deal with it?
I’ll deal with it right away
Do you think there’s something wrong with Wolffy being in such a hurry with us?
Won’t you know when he comes?
what is that
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Wolffy what is this
These are my inventions
But Wolnie won’t let me keep it at home
So I want to store it with you temporarily
Doesn’t look like many
Let’s just take some back each of us.
That’s really troublesome for you guys.
This is too many
Let me see what’s there
this magnet
Isn’t this the Powerful Magnet you used to catch goats?
This is the Big & Little Pills
I seem to have eaten
Stop thinking about it Stop thinking about it
I accidentally got a smoke bomb.
Wolffy, are you okay?
These are Dancing Shoes
I accidentally crossed it and you caught me
And these Spring Shoes
You wore it to jump into Goats’ Village and catch goats.
Opposite Hammer
This is what I used to catch you then.
These are all interesting inventions from the past.
Who said that? I also have a great new invention, okay?
Like this durian bomb, watermelon bomb, boomerang bomb
Each one is powerful
What are you doing so far away?
Let’s help you save the less dangerous ones.
Let’s go home first
Weslie, you are the best
you misunderstood
to thank you
You can pick any one of these inventions
I’ll give you a gift
Just pick one
Then I will choose the most powerful one
Should I choose this one or this one?
maybe this
Then let me do this
What’s this
Good taste
This is the Super Sticker that I carefully designed when I was in the Invention Camp
allowing your body copy other people’s super powers
Copy Sticker?
right
Just stick it on like this
Just shake hands like this and you can copy the other person’s super power.
But nothing happened now
That’s because I don’t have super powers
Forget it, I’ll study it again when I have a chance.
Drag your stuff back to my house
Okay
I really trouble you this time.
Little thing, I didn’t expect you to keep all these inventions
Of course, these inventions are not just the result of my hard work.
And it also carries the memories of so many adventures with you.
Sometimes I wonder what it would be like if we didn’t become friends
Then maybe I would have eaten goats already
Beautiful thought
What sound?
How could there be a hole?
No wonder the longer we drag it, the lighter it becomes
I’m going to pick up the inventions that fell over there.
What’s going on?
What is this?
Why are there rifts here?
Something bad happened
Very powerful suction
Unfortunately, the wind is getting stronger and stronger
Why are these inventions still here?
Weslie
Where are you?
Why is the wind so strong?
what happened
Are there any goats? Save the wolf.
Where is this?
What are you doing to Green Green Grassland?
Do you want to stop me? Let me see what you can do
Wool and gears merged
What are you doing?
You can’t escape
Where is my invention?
Weslie
Give you a little star
Here comes another one
Wolffy
What’s the situation? Who is that guy?
I don’t know. Maybe he also made the rifts on the grassland and here.
I’m fine
Difficult guy
Please play with toys
Toys are integrated
I still have this
You pissed me off
Weslie
What
There’s movement over there
what happened
that is
rift
Get the other parts back for me
To be continued